export const reactTest = [
  {
    question:
      "What is the most useful hook to manage states in the whole application among react hooks?",
    answers: [
      "To manage global state in a Redux-like pattern.",
      "useContext",
      "To optimize performance with memoization.",
      "To navigate between screens in a single-page application.",
      "To handle form inputs.",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the primary purpose of the useState hook in React.js?",
    answers: [
      "To navigate between screens in a single-page application.",
      "To fetch data or execute side effects in functional components.",
      "To handle form inputs.",
      "To manage stateful logic within functional components.",
      "To synchronize state to local storage.",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 3,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which hook in React.js allows you to create a mutable reference that persists across re-renders?",
    answers: [
      "To optimize performance with memoization.",
      "useRef",
      "To navigate between screens in a single-page application.",
      "To synchronize state to local storage.",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1,
  },
  {
    question: "When might you use the useContext hook in a React application?",
    answers: [
      "To access context data without nesting components.",
      "To navigate between screens in a single-page application.",
      "To handle form inputs.",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which hook is commonly used for accessing the current state value and updating it in functional components?",
    answers: [
      "useState",
      "To optimize performance with memoization.",
      "To manage global state in a Redux-like pattern.",
      "To handle form inputs.",
      "To navigate between screens in a single-page application.",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "In a React.js application, what is the significance of the indexOfCurrentAnswer property in the provided structure?",
    answers: [
      "To optimize performance with memoization.",
      "It indicates the index of the correct answer in the array of possible answers.",
      "To navigate between screens in a single-page application.",
      "To fetch data or execute side effects in functional components.",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1,
  },
];

export const htmlTest = [
  {
    question: "What does the acronym HTML stand for?",
    answers: [
      "Hyper Text Markup Language",
      "Highly Technical Markup Language",
      "Home Tool Markup Language",
      "Hyperlinks and Text Markup Language",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which tag is used to define a hyperlink in HTML?",
    answers: ["<a>", "<link>", "<href>", "<hyperlink>"],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "Which tag is used to define an unordered list in HTML?",
    answers: ["<ul>", "<ol>", "<li>", "<ulist>"],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What does the <img> tag do in HTML?",
    answers: [
      "Defines an image",
      "Defines a paragraph",
      "Defines a link",
      "Defines a list item",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question: "What is the purpose of the <p> tag in HTML?",
    answers: [
      "Defines a paragraph",
      "Defines an image",
      "Defines a link",
      "Defines a list item",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  },
  {
    question:
      "What is the significance of the indexOfCorrectAnswer property in this HTML quiz structure?",
    answers: [
      "It indicates the index of the correct answer in the array of possible answers.",
      "To define the position of the question in the quiz sequence.",
      "To determine the difficulty level of the question.",
      "To specify the HTML tag associated with the correct answer.",
    ],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  },
];
